

AFDI FAUZUL BAHAR

SOFTWARE ENGINEER | BACKEND ENGINEER

- **** 081273395212
- https://afdi-portofolio-page.vercel.app/
- ▼ KAB. BANGUNTAPAN, D.I. YOGYAKARTA

SUMMARY

Back-end engineer with 2 years working experience. can learn quickly. has experience working across fields such as software engineers, IT Support, journalists, and reporters. Just an ordinary human and being who always wants to challenge himself to be more valuable

EXPERIENCE

Associate Software Engineer

04/2022 - Present

ICUBE BY SIRCLO

- · Work on E-Commerce developed by Magento, Plugin and Other Customization
- · Create, Edit and Simple Test on GraphQl, Customization Magent
- · On Product Division

IT Support 04/2021 - 04/2022

YAYASAN NURUL HUDA LAMPUNG

- · Maintain all of the technology that is owned
- · Make sure the information system is still excellent, Update feature by leader request
- · Make sure the networking is running normally, debugging when disconnected, and update the networking
- · Stand by for request and instruction about information technology

Intern Full Stack Developer 12/2020 - 02/2021

DEPARTMENT IT YAYASAN NURUL HUDA LAMPUNG

- · Learning about Highchart Js, Material-UI, Architecture Software
- Developed Dashboard Finance of Yayasan Nurul Huda Lampung

Laboratory Assistant Database

INSTITUT TEKNOLOGI SUMATERA

02/2020 - 08/2020

- Introction Database
- · Assisting Practicant to Execution the Data Definition Language
- Assisting Practicant to Execution the Data Manipulation Language
- · Assisting Practicant to Create Simple App to Create Read Update Delete

Laboratory Assistant of Introdcution to Computer and Software II

02/2019 - 08/2020

INSTITUT TEKNOLOGI SUMATERA

- Intro to Structure Data
- · Teach and Assist Practicant to learn about virtual machine,

basic programming using C++ in general

Laboratory Assistant of Algorithms and Data Structure

INSTITUT TEKNOLOGI SUMATERA

- · Intro to Structure Data
- Teach and Assist Practicant about the module

08/2019 - 12/2019

Laboratory Assistant of Algorithms and Programming

INSTITUT TEKNOLOGI SUMATERA

- Intro to Algorithm
- Teach and Assist Practicant to Write Simple Code from Algorithm

Laboratory Assistant of Introdcution to Computer and Software I

09/2018 - 12/2019

INSTITUT TEKNOLOGI SUMATERA

• Teach and Assist first year student about using Microsoft Office softwares such as Ms. Word, Ms. Power Point & Ms. Excel. Also introduce VBA to create Macros in Ms. Excel

EDUCATION

INFORMATICS ENGINEERING 2024

STATE ISLAMIC UNIVERSITY OF SUNAN KALIJAGA - GRADUATE DEGREE

· Awardee of Santri Berprestasi Scholarship

INFORMATICS ENGINEERING 2021

SUMATERA INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY - BACHELOR DEGREE

- Graduated very satisfactory 3.4+ GPA
- · Served as chairman of the student Senate commission I for the 2021 academic year
- · Volunteer each week to teach child who are orphans, homeless and isolated villages on 2019
- · Crew Coding Club Informatics Itera (Complexity)
- · Coordinator Club of Science Data Informatics Itera
- · Awardee of Lampung Provincial Government Scholarship

SCIENCE 2017

TRI SUKSES BOARDING SCHOOL - SENIOR HIGH SCHOOL

- First Best Graduate in Academics
- · First Best Graduate in Non-Academic Field
- · Chairman of Student Council

SKILLS

ReactJs **Beginner** Rest API Intermediate NodeJs C++ Advanced Beginner Laravel Intermediate SQL Advanced AJAX Advanced Intermediate Javascript MySql Advanced **JSON** Intermediate HTML Advanced Magento Intermediate CSS Intermediate ExpressJs Beginner PHP Advanced Intermediate Management Docker Beginner Leadership Advanced

GraphQl Intermediate

LANGUAGES

English Intermediate Indonesia Fluent